[
  {
    "question": "IAM Service is a Regional Service",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "IAM Service is a Service in:",
    "options": [
      "Networking and Content Delivery Service Category",
      "Storage Service Category",
      "Security, identity, and compliance Service Category",
      "Compute Service Category"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Following Services is a Storage Service?",
    "options": [
      "EC2",
      "Amazon S3",
      "Route 53",
      "AWS Organizations"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Following Services is a Compute Service?",
    "options": [
      "EC2",
      "Amazon S3",
      "Route 53",
      "AWS Organizations"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "EC2 is a Regional Service?",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "A regional service is a service that operates across multiple regions or have a global presence.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following services is used to control access to AWS services for users",
    "options": [
      "EC2",
      "Amazon S3",
      "IAM",
      "AWS Organizations"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following services is used to protect against DDoS attacks.",
    "options": [
      "AWS Cognito",
      "AWS Shield",
      "IAM",
      "Amazon CloudWatch"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which component of the AWS Global Infrastructure does Amazon CloudFront ensure low-latency delivery?",
    "options": [
      "AWS Regions",
      "AWS edge locations",
      "AWS Availability Zones",
      "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC)"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "You can run applications and workloads from a Region closer to the end users to ____ latency.",
    "options": [
      "increase",
      "decrease"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Networking, storage, compute, and databases are examples of service categories that AWS offers.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are geographic areas that host two or more Availability Zones",
    "options": [
      "AWS Origins",
      "AWS Regions",
      "Compute zones",
      "Edge locations"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "____ means the infrastructure has built-in component redundancy and ____ means that resources dynamically adjust to increases or decreases in capacity requirements.",
    "options": [
      "No human intervention, fault tolerant",
      "Elastic and scalable, no human intervention",
      "Fault tolerant, elastic and scalable",
      "Fault tolerant, no human intervention",
      "Elastic and scalable, fault tolerant"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Availability Zones within a Region are connected through low-latency links.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these statements about Availability Zones is not true?",
    "options": [
      "Availability Zones are designed for fault isolation.",
      "Availability Zones are made up of one or more data centers.",
      "A data center can be used for more than one Availability Zone.",
      "Availability Zones are connected to each other using high-speed private link"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is true about Regions? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "Each Region is located in a separate geographic area.",
      "A Region is a physical location that has multiple Availability Zones.",
      "They are the physical locations of your customers.",
      "All Regions are located in one specific geographic area."
    ],
    "correctIndex": [
      0,
      1
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "AWS highly recommends provisioning your compute resources across ____ Availability Zones.",
    "options": [
      "all",
      "multiple",
      "no",
      "single"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False? Edge locations are only located in the same general area as Regions.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 1
  }
]